Finding Aid for School of Natural Resources and Environment (University of Michigan) Records 1903-2012.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs, 1904-2003
    - School of Natural Resources
      - Faculty
        - Craig, Robert, undated (Box 70)
        - Craine, Lyle E., undated (Box 70)
        - Cramer, Christine, undated (Box 70)
        - Crow, Thomas, undated (Box 70)
        - Crowfoot, James, undated (Box 70)
        - Dana, Samuel Trask, 1976 (Box 70)
        - Daneke, Gregory A., undated (Box 70)
        - Davis, Kenneth P., undated (Box 70)
        - DeYoung, Raymond, undated (Box 70)
        - Diana, James, undated (Box 70)
        - Dickinson, Fred E., undated (Box 70)
        - Dils, Robert E., undated (Box 70)
        - Dorr, John A., undated (Box 70)
        - Dougherty, Joanna, 1988; undated (Box 70)
        - Drake, William D., undated (Box 70)
        - Duke, Richard, undated (Box 70)
        - Eisendrath, Charles, undated (Box 70)
        - Ellis, Everett L., undated (Box 70)
        - Erickson, Donna L., undated (Box 70)
        - Feldt, Allan G., undated (Box 70)
        - Foran, Jeff, undated (Box 70)
        - Fowler, Gary, 1985; undated (Box 70)
        - Franz, Norman C., undated (Box 70)
        - Gladwin, Thomas N., undated (Box 70)
        - Graham-Tomasi, Ted, undated (Box 70)
        - Grandison, Kenrick Ian, undated (Box 70)
        - Gregory, Gustav Robinson, undated (Box 70)
        - Grese, Robert E., undated (Box 70)
        - Hales, David, 1984; 1988; undated (Box 70)
        - Hatcher, Charles, undated (Box 70)
        - Helfand, Gloria, undated (Box 70)
        - Hill, Cary L., undated (Box 70)
        - Hooper, Frank, undated (Box 70)
        - Hunt, George S., undated (Box 71)
        - Jaeger, Gil, undated (Box 71)
        - Jensen, Alvin, undated (Box 71)
        - Johnson, Carl W., undated (Box 71)
        - Jones, Carol, undated (Box 71)
        - Kadlec, John A., undated (Box 71)
        - Kaplan, Rachel, undated (Box 71)
        - Kauffman, Calvin H., undated (Box 71)
        - Keoleian, Greg, undated (Box 71)
        - Kerfoot, Charles, undated (Box 71)
        - Kiel, Donald F., undated (Box 71)
        - Klein, Andrea, 1987 (Box 71)
        - Knight, Fred B., undated (Box 71)
        - Kynoch, William, undated (Box 71)
        - Lagler, Karl, 1978 (Box 71)
        - Latta, W. Carl, undated (Box 71)
        - Leonard, Justin W., undated (Box 71)
        - Lovejoy, Parish S., undated (Box 71)
        - Low, Bobbi, undated (Box 71)
        - MacDonald, Neil, undated (Box 71)
        - MacKinnon, Douglas A., undated (Box 71)
        - Mangnall, Richard C., undated (Box 71)
        - Marquis, Stewart, undated (Box 71)
        - Marra, Alan A., undated (Box 71)
        - Martin, Lee R., 1963 (Box 71)
        - Mazmanian, Daniel A., undated (Box 71)
        - McEwen, Douglas, undated (Box 71)
        - McFadden, James T., undated (Box 71)
        - Meier, Richard L., 1957 (Box 71)
        - Miller, Kenton R., 1978; undated (Box 71)
        - Miller, Pat, undated (Box 71)
        - Milne, Robert, undated (Box 71)
        - Mohai, Paul, undated (Box 71)
        - Moore, Michael R., undated (Box 71)
        - Morton, Harrison L., undated (Box 71)
        - Muller, Hugh, undated (Box 71)
        - Murray, Betty Jean, 1988; undated (Box 71)
        - Murray, Frank (Box 76)
        - Nassauer, Joan, undated (Box 71)
        - Newman, Sandra, undated (Box 71)
        - Newmark, Bill, undated (Box 71)
        - Nowak, Paul, undated (Box 71)
        - Olson, Chuck W., undated (Box 71)
        - Patronsky, Louis A., undated (Box 71)
        - Perfecto, Ivette, undated (Box 71)
        - Polakowski, Kenneth, undated (Box 71)
        - Pollack, Peter, undated (Box 71)
        - Porter, Harry W., 1965 (Box 71)
        - Porter, James, undated (Box 71)
        - Preston, Stephen B., undated (Box 71)
        - Princen, Tom, undated (Box 71)
        - Rabe, Dale, undated (Box 71)
        - Ramsdell, Willett, undated (Box 71)
        - Richards, Paul, undated (Box 71)
        - Richardson, Curtis, undated (Box 71)
        - Robbins, John A., undated (Box 71)
        - Robinson, William (Box 71)
        - Rollet, Ronald, 1978 (Box 71)
        - Root, Terry, 1988; undated (Box 71)
        - Sandman, Peter, undated (Box 71)
        - Say, Wayne, undated (Box 71)
        - Scheele, Robert F., 1979; undated (Box 71)
        - Schelske, Claire L., undated (Box 71)
        - Schoenmann, Lee R., undated (Box 71)
        - Schramm, Gunter, undated (Box 71)
        - Searle, William L, undated (Box 76)
          (poster for Theodore Roosevelt Professorship of Ecosystems Management)
        - Shadley, Carole, undated (Box 71)
        - Shapiro, Kenneth, undated (Box 71)
        - Sharpe, Grant W., undated (Box 71)
        - Smith, Fred E., 1950 (Box 71)
        - Smith, Glenn, undated (Box 71)
        - Smith, Stanford, undated (Box 71)
        - Soule, Michael, 1988; undated (Box 71)
        - Spalding, Volney Morgan, circa, 1915 (Box 71)
        - Sponsler, Olenus Lee, circa, 1930 (Box 71)
        - Spurr, Stephen, undated; 1 folders; 1 oversize photographs located in box 76 (Box 71)
        - Stanley, Jan, undated (Box 71)
        - Stapp, William, 1987-1991; undated (Box 71)
        - Stoermer, Eugene, undated (Box 71)
        - Stoffle, Richard, undated (Box 71)
        - Suits, Gwynn, undated (Box 71)
        - Svenson, Erik A., undated (Box 71)
        - Swierzbinski, Joseph, undated (Box 71)
        - Talbot, Janet F., undated (Box 71)
        - Thomas, Tom D., 1978 (Box 71)
        - Thomson, Thomas, undated (Box 71)
        - Tucker, Richard, undated (Box 71)
        - Wadsworth, Frank H., undated (Box 71)
        - Wagner, Warren, undated (Box 71)
        - Wang, Tom, undated (Box 71)
        - Watson, Russell, undated (Box 71)
        - Weaver, Richard L., undated (Box 71)
        - Webb, Paul, undated (Box 71)
        - West, Patrick, undated (Box 71)
        - White, David, undated (Box 71)
        - Wiley, Mike, undated (Box 71)
        - Witter, John, undated (Box 71)
        - Wondolleck, Julia M., 1987; undated (Box 71)
        - Woodman, Ernest, undated (Box 71)
        - Yaffee, Steven, 1984; undated (Box 71)
        - Young, Bug?, undated (Box 71)
        - Zahner, Robert, undated (Box 71)
        - Zimmerman, Floyd W., 1964 (Box 71)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 71)
      - National Conservation Training Center, 2002 (Box 71)
        (16 folders, includes negatives)
      - Paul Bunyan Ball, undated (Box 71)
      - Saginaw Forest, 1904-1945; undated; 8 photographs (Box 71)
        (oversize located in oversize folder in Box 76)
      - Staff, undated (Box 71)
      - Students
        - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 71)
        - Projects and Presentations, 2000 (Box 71)
    - Michigan
      - Golden Lake, Camp Filibert Roth, 1942 (Box 71)
  - Glass Slides of Michigan
    - Michigan State Highway Traffic Map, 1929 (Box 50A)
    - Upper Peninsula
      - Baraga County, Three Lakes from M-28 (Box 50A)
      - Baraga State Park (Box 50A)
      - Charcoal Kilns (historic), west of Munising (Box 50A)
      - Dodge Munuscong State Park, 3 slides (Box 50A)
      - Drummond Island, Old English Fort (Box 50A)
      - Fort Wilkins State Park, 5 slides (Box 50A)
      - Grand Island (Box 50A)
      - Highway 6 to Eagle Harbor (Box 50A)
      - Highway 94, Munising to Marquette, 2 slides (Box 50A)
      - Huron Mountains
        - Ives Lake, 2 slides (Box 50A)
        - Lake Independence (Box 50A)
        - Road to Huron Mountain Club (Box 50A)
        - State Highway Bridge (Box 50A)
      - Iron County Cattle Ranch (Box 50A)
      - Isle Royale
        - Camp at Gull Rock (Box 50A)
        - Cliff on North Side of Blake Point (Box 50A)
        - Daisy Farm/Civilian Conservation Corps Camp (Box 50A)
        - Daisy Farm Trail (Box 50A)
        - Duncan Bay, 2 slides (Box 50A)
        - Fire of 1936 at Siskowit Bay (includes aftermath), 1938; 20 slides (Box 50A)
        - McCargoes Cove, 2 slides (Box 50A)
        - Monument Rock (Box 50A)
        - Mott Island (Box 50A)
        - Old Lighthouse near Site of Ransom (Box 50A)
        - Rock Harbor
          - Lighthouse (Box 50A)
          - Small Island near, 4 slides (Box 50A)
          - Steamer landing (Box 50A)
          - Trail Construction on Greenstone Ridge (Box 50A)
        - Sargent Lake (Box 50A)
        - Siskowit Bay
          - Greenstone Ridge Trail (Box 50A)
          - Small Island in (Box 50A)
          - Trees and Lumber, 3 slides (Box 50A)
          - View from Senter Point (Box 50A)
        - Siskowit Lake Outlet, 2 slides (Box 50A)
      - Keweenaw Golf Course (Box 50A)
      - Lake Michigamme (Box 50A)
      - Lake Superior Highway, south of Emerson (Box 50A)
      - Mackinac Island, 2 slides (Box 50A)
      - Marquette State Park (Box 50A)
      - Menominee River, 3 slides (Box 50B)
      - Pictured Rocks (Box 50B)
      - Porcupine Mountains, 6 slides (Box 50B)
      - Portage Canal (Box 50B)
      - Saint Ignace (Box 50B)
      - Tahquamenon River and Falls, 17 slides (Box 50B)
      - Trunk Line Highway (Box 50B)
      - Wells State Park (map) (Box 50B)
    - Northern Lower Michigan
      - Au Sable River, 2 slides (Box 50B)
      - Bay City State Park (Box 50B)
      - Camp Algonquin, Burt Lake, 3 slides (Box 50B)
      - Camp Hayo-Went-Ha, Torch Lake, 2 slides (Box 50B)
      - Cheboygan County Soil Erosion (Box 50B)
      - Glen Haven State Park, 2 slides (Box 50B)
      - Harrisville State Park, 2 slides (Box 50B)
      - Hartwick Pines State Park, 2 slides (Box 50B)
      - Higgins Lake State Park, 3 slides (Box 50B)
      - Hubbard Lake, 6 slides (Box 50B)
      - Ludington State Park, 8 slides
        - Slides 1-4 (Box 50B)
        - Slides 5-8 (Box 50C)
      - Petoskey, 3 slides (Box 50C)
      - Wilderness State Park (map) (Box 50C)
    - Southern Lower Michigan
      - Ann Arbor
        - Allmendinger Park (Box 50C)
        - Cascade Glen Drive, 1914 (Box 50C)
        - Edison Company Home (Box 50C)
        - Forest Hills Cemetery (Box 50C)
        - Fosters Bridge over Huron River (Box 50C)
        - Grade Crossing at Fosters (Box 50C)
        - Island Park, 2 slides (Box 50C)
        - Main and William Streets, 1933 (Box 50C)
        - Mullett Creek, 1914 (Box 50C)
        - Mullett Pond, 1914; 2 slides (Box 50C)
        - Packard Road Residences, 2 slides (Box 50C)
        - Pi Beta Phi Chapter House (Box 50C)
        - Stevens, F.W., Garden of, 2 slides (Box 50C)
        - Stone School Road (Box 50C)
        - Tealdi Garden, 6 slides (Box 50C)
        - Tilley, Morris P., Plan for Residence of, 1911 (Box 50C)
        - University of Michigan Central Campus Trees and Foliage, 1929; 5 slides (Box 50C)
        - Warthin, A.S., Residence of, 4 slides (Box 50C)
      - Belle Isle, 7 slides (Box 50C)
      - Bloomer State Park (Box 50C)
      - Brighton, Turner Farm (Box 50C)
      - Camp Unzer, Jackson County (Box 50C)
      - Clinton River
        - Boat Harbor (Box 50C)
        - Dawson's Dam in Pontiac (Box 50C)
        - Dump (Box 50C)
        - Homes on River (Box 50C)
        - Mount Clemens (Box 50C)
        - Mouth (Box 50C)
        - Swiss Valley Park Entrance (Box 50C)
        - Upper River (Box 50C)
        - Utica, 2 slides (Box 50C)
        - View (Box 50C)
      - Cranbrook Institute, 8 slides (Box 50C)
      - Detroit
        - Rouge Parkway (Box 50C)
        - Woodlawn Cemetery, 7 slides (Box 50C)
      - Dexter-Huron Park, 3 slides (Box 50C)
      - Dexter Mansion (Box 50C)
      - Edison Lake/Edison Club (Box 50C)
      - Farm Plans
        - Brandt, Russell (Shiawassee County) (Box 50C)
        - Ortner, Leonard (Saginaw County) (Box 50C)
      - Fleming Creek, Roberts Farm (topographical map) (Box 50C)
      - Grand Rapids, Tree Moving, 1927; 7 slides (Box 50C)
      - Grosse Pointe
        - Alger, Russel A., Estate (Box 50C)
        - Newberry Estate (Box 50C)
      - Hartland
        - Cromaine Library (Box 50C)
        - Crouse Farm (Box 50C)
        - Franklin School, 2 slides (Box 50C)
        - High School, 4 slides (Box 50C)
        - Methodist Church, 3 slides (Box 50C)
        - Old Congregational Church (Box 50C)
        - Village (aerial view) (Box 50C)
        - Waldenwoods, 4 slides (Box 50C)
      - Huron-Clinton Parkway Maps
        - General, 2 slides (Box 50C)
        - Bathing Beaches (Box 50C)
        - Children's Camps (Box 50C)
        - Golf Courses (Box 50C)
        - Private Parks (Box 50C)
        - State Parks (Box 50C)
      - Huron River
        - Above Superior Dam (Box 50C)
        - Ann Arbor Swimming Beach (Box 50C)
        - Barton Dam, view near (Box 50C)
        - Barton Dam and Powerhouse (Box 50C)
        - Bridge, unidentified (Box 50C)
        - Camp (Box 50C)
        - Day Camp below Ann Arbor (Box 50C)
        - Delhi Bridge (sign) (Box 50C)
        - Ford Dam (Box 50C)
        - Ford Lake, 5 slides (Box 50C)
        - French Landing Garbage Reduction Plant (Box 50C)
        - Lakeland (Box 50C)
        - Oxbow Lake, view near (Box 50C)
        - Oxbow Lake Outlet (Box 50C)
        - Pontiac Lake (source) (Box 50C)
        - Portage Lake, Dammed Outlet (Box 50C)
        - Portage Lake, School Buses (Box 50C)
        - Railroad Bridge (Box 50C)
        - Rockwood Golf Course (Box 50C)
        - Susterka Lake Fisheries (Box 50C)
        - Ypsilanti
          - Potential Park (Box 50C)
          - Tourist Camp (Box 50C)
          - View (Box 50C)
      - Island Lake State Park (Box 50C)
      - Midland Courthouse, 2 slides (Box 50C)
      - Muskegon State Park (Box 50C)
      - Washtenaw County Collecting Grounds (map) (Box 50C)
      - Waterloo and Clear Lake (Box 50C)
      - Williamston Kettle Hole Project, 2 slides (Box 50C)
      - Ypsilanti, Ford Factory (Box 50C)
    - Douglas Lake Release Cutting, 1931; 1 boxes (Box 72)
    - Miscellaneous, 1 boxes (Box 72)
    - Saginaw Forest, 1915-1925; 6 boxes (Box 72)
    - Stinchfield Woods, 3 boxes (Box 72)
    - Tree Species, 11 slides in plastic bag (Box 72)
    - Unidentified, 1 boxes (Box 72)
  - Negatives
    - 100th Anniversary (Box 71)
    - Faculty
      - Brewer, Garry D., undated (Box 71)
      - Crowfoot, James, undated (Box 71)
      - Stapp, William, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Slides
    - Camp Filibert Roth, 1980s (Box 71)
    - Camp Hayo-Went-Ha, 1998 (Box 71)
    - Classes
      - 587 (Box 71)
      - 590 (Box 71)
      - 591 (Box 71)
      - 688 (Box 71)
      - 787 (Box 71)
      - 791 (Box 71)
- Audiovisual
  - General
    - Betamax
      - Forestry Sequences -- Saginaw Forest, Camp Filibert Roth, 1928 (Box 73)
      - School Movies, 1928 (Box 73)
        (First Forestry Alumni Reunion, Field Day at Saginaw Forest, Camp Filibert Roth)
      - The Idea of Michigan, undated (Box 73)
      - Michigans Neglected Resource -- Status of Michigan Farming, undated (Box 73)
      - Mutts, Michael, Fading Family Farm, 1981 (Box 73)
        (submitted for practicum)
    - VHS
      - Forestry Sequences -- Saginaw Forest, Camp Filibert Roth, 1928; 3 tapes (Box 73)
      - Banzhaf/Backiel, 2003 (Box 73)
      - Bierbaum, Rosina, undated (Box 73)
      - Browner, Carole M., 2002 (Box 73)
      - Cargas, Martin, 2006 (Box 73)
      - Colwell, Rita, 2007 (Box 73)
      - Emeritus Lunch, 2002 (Box 73)
      - First Annual Peter M. Wege Lecture, 2001 (Box 73)
      - JJR Lecture, Dirk Wascher, 2006 (Box 73)
      - Keoleian, Greg, Peak Oil, 2006 (Box 73)
      - McDonough, William, Sustainable Development, 1999 (Box 73)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Lecture, Majora Carter, 2007 (Box 73)
      - Remarks of John C. Gordon (Box 73)
      - Undergraduate Programs, undated (Box 73)
    - Film Reels
      - Camp Filibert Roth, undated; 2 reels (Box 74)
      - Field Day, 1930 (Box 74)
      - Lumbering in the Pacific Northwest, undated (Box 74)
      - Western Logging, 1930s (Box 74)
    - Cassettes
      - Bierbaum, Rosina, Sundance Summit Lecture, undated (Box 75)
      - Theodore Roosevelt Professorship, 1996 (Box 75)
    - CDs
      - Awards Ceremony, 2006 (Box 75)
      - Bierbaum, Rosina
        - Lectures and Interviews, 2006-2007; undated (Box 75)
        - Photos, 2006 (Box 75)
      - Commencement, 2003 (Box 75)
      - Greening of Dana Presentation, 2001 (Box 75)
      - MELDI Conference, undated (Box 75)
      - Miscellaneous, 2000s; 2 folders (Box 75)
      - Orientation, 2005-2006 (Box 75)
      - Retirements, 2006 (Box 75)
        (Terry Brown and Burt Barnes)
      - Solstice Party, 2005 (Box 75)
      - Stewards Newsletter Material, 2007 (Box 75)
      - Student Photo Contest, 2006 (Box 75)
  - Department of Landscape Architecture
    - Betacam SP
      - BCT-20MA
        - General Program Information, undated (Box 75)
      - BCT-60MLA
        - Miscellaneous, undated; 2 tapes (Box 75)
    - Hi8
      - Bob Grese, Ken Polakowski, and Ian Grandison, undated; 3 tapes (Box 75)
    - U-Matic
      - Ian McHarg Speaks to Landscape Architecture Class, undated (Box 75)
    - VHS
      - General Program Information, undated; 3 tapes (Box 75)
- Academic Affairs Committee
  Academic Affairs Committee (.5 linear feet) contains the minutes of meetings and correspondence of the committee from 1988 to 1994. Because these committee records comment on student performance they are restricted in accordance with the access policies outlined in Access and Use Section
  - 1988-1990 (Box 53)
  - 1990-1991 (Box 53)
    [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2066 ]
  - 1991-1992 (Box 53)
    [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2067 ]
  - 1992-1993 (Box 53)
    [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2068 ]
  - 1993-1994 (Box 53)
    [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2069 ]
- Concentration Chairs
  Concentration Chairs (.3 linear feet) contains correspondence to the chairs, frequently regarding meetings of the concentration chairs from 1989 to 1993. Topics include curricular requirements for various concentrations within the school.
  - Correspondence, 1989-1993; 4 folders (Box 54)
- University Lands Committee
  The Dean of the School of Natural Resources is chairman of the University Lands Committee The University Lands Committee series (.4 linear feet) contains correspondence and reports concerning university properties. Some of the properties are controlled by the School of Natural Resources and others are not. Correspondence about a particular piece of property is located in a properties subseries. The series spans the years 1965-1983. Box 23 contains earlier material relating to various SNR properties.
  - General Correspondence, 1965-1983; 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Manistee National Forest Classification Program, 1967-1976 (Box 54)
  - Minutes, 1970-1976 (Box 54)
  - Reports, 1967-1976 (Box 54)
  - Oil and Resource Exploration, 1970-1976 (Box 54)
  - Properties
    - Biological Station (Cheboygan County), 1963-1973 (Box 54)
    - E.S. George Reserve (Livingston County), 1962-1982 (Box 54)
    - Ford Fund Land (Marquette County), 1963-1964 (Box 54)
    - Menonaqua Beach (Emmet County) and Palmer (Antrim County)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 54)
    - Missaukee County Reserve, 1974-1981 (Box 54)
    - Rocket Launch Site (Keewenaw County), 1972-1982 (Box 54)
    - Saugatuck (Allegan County), 1972 (Box 54)
    - Sugar Island (Chippewa County), 1942-1975; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Wilson Wildlife Refuge (Livingston County), 1971-1975 (Box 54)
- Department of Landscape Architecture
  The series Department of Landscape Architecture is comprised of two subseries: Alumni Correspondence and Other Correspondence. The former includes a collection of correspondence between students and alumni of the Department and two professors, Aubrey Tealdi and H.O. Whittemore. The correspondence spans 1917 to 1960, with the bulk of the correspondence occurring between 1930 and 1955. The majority of the correspondence is with Professor Whittemore. It is arranged in reverse chronological order by the alumni's last name. The first set of folders include, correspondence with alumni, from which only one letter was received; this follows the arrangement of the original owners, Tealdi and Whittemore. The correspondence ranges from suggestions of possible employment openings to retirement congratulations to past students. It also includes discussion of work and theory as well as general status updates. The breadth of time covered by some correspondence is impressive, in some cases the alumni corresponded with their professors over a twenty to thirty-year period. This information can act as an informal longitudinal survey of the activities of Department alumni. It is especially interesting to learn about the work available to women alumnae, to follow the progression of careers during the Depression, World War II, and the post-War era, as well as to note the different positions taken by alumni all over the country. Among the correspondents are alumni who worked on government projects, including the Tennessee Valley Authority, and others who went on to become respected landscape architecture faculty at other institutions.
  The small sub-series of Other Correspondence includes letters from Professor Tealdi regarding the administration of the Nichols Arboretum, and letters to Professor Whittemore from prospective students requesting information about the Department and about the field of landscape architecture, along with his responses.
  - Alumni Correspondence, 1917-1960
    - A-C, 1929-1938 (Box 54)
    - D-F, 1925-1958 (Box 54)
    - G-L, 1939-1948 (Box 54)
    - M-O, 1926-1960 (Box 54)
    - P-R, 1931-1947 (Box 54)
    - T-W, 1940 (Box 54)
    - Andresen, Arvid, 1936-1954 (Box 55)
    - Armstrong, Thelma, 1938 (Box 55)
    - Aust, Franz, 1917-1939 (Box 55)
    - Barker, George H., 1929-1956 (Box 55)
    - Beck, Robert, 1936 (Box 55)
    - Beens, John, 1932-1942 (Box 55)
    - Bourquin, Alice, 1935-1953 (Box 55)
    - Bourquin, Jessie, 1934-1953 (Box 55)
    - Bushey, Donald, 1923-1959 (Box 55)
    - Cavendish, Virginia, 1933-1943 (Box 55)
    - Champlin, Hannah, 1930-1948 (Box 55)
    - Clark, Harry, 1934-1937 (Box 55)
    - Clegg, Gilbert, 1936-1941 (Box 55)
    - Conger, Iliff, 1930-1934 (Box 55)
    - Crawford, Jack, 1929-1960 (Box 55)
    - Cuthbert, Frederick, 1928-1957 (Box 55)
    - Digiulio, Giulio, 1946-1949 (Box 55)
    - Durfee, Dorthy, 1936-1952 (Box 55)
    - Fairbank, Chandler, 1934-1946 (Box 55)
    - Frissell, J. Martin, 1930-1947 (Box 55)
    - Gish, Russell, 1929-1956 (Box 55)
    - Godshalk, Clarence, 1928-1955 (Box 55)
    - Gray, William, 1929-1941 (Box 55)
    - Grever, Earl, 1929-1954 (Box 55)
    - Griffing, M. Scudder, 1938-1941 (Box 55)
    - Hall, Miriam, 1936-1958 (Box 55)
    - Hayward, George, 1936-1950 (Box 55)
    - Holkeboer, Peter, 1932-1946
    - Hull, Roy, 1924-1955 (Box 55)
    - Kennedy, Gordon, 1931-1944 (Box 55)
    - Lamley, Hubert, 1927-1947 (Box 55)
    - Larkin, Dennis, 1957-1958 (Box 55)
    - Laverty, Wayne, 1929-1952 (Box 55)
    - Lease, Thomas, 1932-1946 (Box 55)
    - Legg, William, 1929-1941 (Box 55)
    - Leppelmeier, Gilbert, 1930-1955 (Box 55)
    - Martin, Ruth, 1939-1941 (Box 55)
    - McCallum, James, 1935-1953 (Box 55)
    - McGillivray, Donald, 1936-1958 (Box 55)
    - McKelvey, Walter, 1925-1955 (Box 55)
    - McMillan, David, 1925-1943 (Box 55)
    - Miller, Daniel, 1926-1930 (Box 55)
    - Morgan, Willard, 1939-1944 (Box 55)
    - Northon, Harold, 1949-1960 (Box 55)
    - Peterson, John, 1931-1939 (Box 55)
    - Piester, Everett, 1926-1957 (Box 55)
    - Ralston, Elizabeth, 1928-1935 (Box 55)
    - Ratcliff, Russell, 1930-1952 (Box 55)
    - Reynolds, Eugene, 1937-1960 (Box 55)
    - Robinson, Florence, 1932-1949 (Box 55)
    - Roehl, Arnold, 1926-1947 (Box 55)
    - Schroeder, Jeanette, 1936-1960 (Box 55)
    - Seeley, DeLos, 1936-1956 (Box 55)
    - Shoemaker, Mark, 1929-1947 (Box 55)